<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>To Echo The World</title><link>https://srividyasuresh.github.io/toEchoTheWorld/</link><description>Recent content on To Echo The World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://srividyasuresh.github.io/toEchoTheWorld/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On being a (temporary) pet parent, multiple times</title><link>https://srividyasuresh.github.io/toEchoTheWorld/thoughts/onbeingapetparent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://srividyasuresh.github.io/toEchoTheWorld/thoughts/onbeingapetparent/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="on-being-a-temporary-pet-parent-multiple-times">On being a (temporary) pet parent, multiple times&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Ever since I remember, I&amp;rsquo;d always been afraid of animals. Be it a cockroach or a friendly golden retriever. I&amp;rsquo;ve run away from them, hid from them, cried from fear, screamed at others too. Even 4 years back, I remember my sister-in-law&amp;rsquo;s cat walking into the hall and me cowering away. Her kittens tried to climb onto my lap, and their claws were the most ferocious things for months. And they were adorable. I could always appreciate their visual appeal. Just, from a distance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://srividyasuresh.github.io/toEchoTheWorld/about-me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://srividyasuresh.github.io/toEchoTheWorld/about-me/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Hello World!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Srividya here. I&amp;rsquo;m a fanatic reader, chocolate hoarder, herbal tea enthusiast, relucatant cook, data nerd, science storyteller, teacher, pet parent, curious artist, travel (over)planner, and.. I&amp;rsquo;ll keep you informed of more, I guess. And in one of these, I&amp;rsquo;ve built a career. The rest remain but humble hobbies that I dedicate my life to.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This has been on my to-do list for a long time. Start a blog. Put my thoughts out into the world. And maybe hear an echo back. My own thoughts are but an echo of the growing sum of me. The me winding through this world, somehow finding my way to your screen.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Creating this GitHub Pages Blog</title><link>https://srividyasuresh.github.io/toEchoTheWorld/techtalk/creatingthisblog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://srividyasuresh.github.io/toEchoTheWorld/techtalk/creatingthisblog/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="journey-of-creating-this-blog-with-ai">Journey of creating this Blog (with AI)&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>I’ve been wanting to start a blog for a while now. Somthing that integrates my love for tech with everything else in my life. I wanted to build it from scratch, make it my own. Cos UI isn&amp;rsquo;t my strongest skill, I kept putting it off for another day, a day when I&amp;rsquo;ll be awesome at HTML, CSS, JS and everything else in between.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>